Guide to the Abraham Hayward correspondence files: 1063 items, 1790-1889
The New York Public Library. Carl H. Pforzheimer Collection of Shelley and His Circle.
- Doyle, Francis Hastings, Sir, 1810-1888, Oxford & Cambridge Club, Pall Mall, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 November [no year]; HWD 06.034; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 December 1858; HWD 02.033; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 November 1857; HWD 01.027; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 October 1857; HWD 01.019; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 May 1859; HWD 01.026; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 May 1859; HWD 01.020; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 May 1857; HWD 01.022; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 November 1859; HWD 02.034; autograph letter signed
- Drummond, Henry, 1786-1860 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 January 1856; HWD 01.023; autograph letter signed
- Duff Gordon, Lucie, Lady, 1821-1869 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Wednesday"; HWD 07.036; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Ava, Frederick Temple Blackwood, Marquis of, 1826-1902 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Tuesday 16 [no year]; HWD 04.023; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Ava, Frederick Temple Blackwood, Marquis of, 1826-1902, 8 Grosvenor Sq - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 April 1869; HWD 02.087; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Ava, Frederick Temple Blackwood, Marquis of, 1826-1902, Government House, Ottawa - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 November 1873; HWD 02.083; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Ava, Frederick Temple Blackwood, Marquis of, 1826-1902, Government House, Ottawa - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 08.063; autograph letter signed (fragment)
- Dufferin and Clandeboye, Helen Selina Blackwood, Baroness, 1807-1867, The Pavilion, Hampstead Heath - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 July 1855; HWD 06.001; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Clandeboye, Helen Selina Blackwood, Baroness, 1807-1867 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 July 1854; HWD 06.002; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Clandeboye, Helen Selina Blackwood, Baroness, 1807-1867 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.006; autograph letter signed
  Addressed to "Dear Combatant".
- Dufferin and Clandeboye, Helen Selina Blackwood, Baroness, 1807-1867, Dufferin Lodge, Highgate - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 February 1858; HWD 06.003; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Clandeboye, Helen Selina Blackwood, Baroness, 1807-1867 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 06.078; autograph letter signed
- Dufferin and Clandeboye, Helen Selina Blackwood, Baroness, 1807-1867 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.007; autograph note signed
  No salutation; begins, "Je wouldrais, si je couldrais.".
  No salutation; begins, "Je wouldrais, si je couldrais....
- Dufferin and Clandeboye, Helen Selina Blackwood, Baroness, 1807-1867, Kghgate - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 July [no year]; MISC 3512; autograph letter signed
- Dukinfield, Henry Robert, Sir, 1791-1858 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 December 1854; HWD 09.059; autograph letter signed
- Dunlop, Alexander Graham, 1814-1892, Cadiz - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 December 1866; HWD 06.016; autograph letter signed
- Dunlop, Alexander Graham, 1814-1892, Cadiz - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 September 1865; HWD 09.026; autograph letter signed
- Dunlop, Alexander Graham, 1814-1892, Cadiz - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 February 1867; HWD 09.028; autograph letter signed
- Dyce Sombré, Mary Anne Jervis, 1812-1893 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 January 1856; HWD 04.066; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914, Granton Hotel - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 August 1870; HWD 01.037; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 August 1853; HWD 01.040; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914, St. Muir's Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January 1855; HWD 01.039; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914, 23 St. James's Place, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 April 1866; HWD 01.034; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914, Gobemuisgach - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 August 1853; HWD 01.038; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 January 1853; HWD 01.035; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 September 1853; HWD 09.004; autograph letter signed
- Elcho, Francis Wemyss-Charteris Douglas, Lord, 1818-1914 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 July 1853; HWD 01.036; autograph letter signed
- Elliot, Elizabeth Howe Bromley, 1824?-1880, 7, Onslow Square. S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.074; autograph letter signed
- Elliot, Frances, 1820-1898, 40 Welbeck St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.033; autograph letter signed
- Ellis, Henry, Sir, 1777-1869 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 December 1854; HWD 10.031; autograph letter signed
- Elwin, Whitwell, 1816-1900, Booton Rectory, Norwich - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 November 1858; HWD 06.070; autograph letter signed
- Elwin, Whitwell, 1816-1900, Booton R. Norwich - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 December 1858; HWD 10.042; autograph letter signed
- Elwin, Whitwell, 1816-1900, Booton Rectory, Norwich - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 February 1859; HWD 06.066; autograph letter signed
- Erle, William, Sir, 1793-1880 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 June 1845; HWD 06.063; autograph letter signed
- Escott, T. H. S. (Thomas Hay Sweet), 1844-1924, 38 Brompton Crescent S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 December 1882; HWD 02.060; autograph letter signed
- Everett, Edward, 1794-1865, 46 Grosvenor Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 August 1845; HWD 08.033; autograph letter signed
- Falkland, Lucius Bentinck Cary, Viscount, 1803-1884, 53 Eaton Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 February 1857; HWD 06.025; autograph letter signed
- Fane, Violet, 1843-1905, Winchfield - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 January [no year]; HWD 05.026; autograph letter signed
- Fane, Violet, 1843-1905 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Saturday"; HWD 03.051; autograph letter signed
- Fane, Violet, 1843-1905, 22 Grosvenor Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14th Saturday; HWD 05.027; autograph letter signed
- Ferguson, Robert, 1799-1865, 125 Park Street, Grosvenor Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 April 1858; HWD 10.043; autograph letter signed
- Finlason, W. F. (William Francis), 1818-1895, Temple - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January 1868; HWD 10.037; autograph letter signed
- Follett, William Webb, Sir, 1798-1845 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 April 1845; HWD 05.087; autograph letter signed
- Fonblanque, Albany, 1793-1872, Board of Trade S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 October [no year]; HWD 02.004; autograph letter signed
- Fonblanque, Albany, 1793-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 January 1834; HWD 10.005; autograph letter signed
- Fonblanque, Albany, 1793-1872, 31 South St. Thurloe Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 July 1880; HWD 02.056; autograph letter signed
- Fonblanque, Albany, 1793-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 April 1838; HWD 05.006; autograph letter signed
- Fonblanque, Albany, 1793-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 July 1836; HWD 10.004; autograph letter signed
- Ford, Richard, 1796-1858, 123 Park Street, Grosvenor Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 March 1849; MISC 3511; autograph letter signed
- Ford, Richard, 1796-1858 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.098; autograph letter signed
- Ford, Richard, 1796-1858, 123 Park Street, Grosvenor Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 January 1857; HWD 07.077; autograph letter signed
  cancelled address panel to: T. L. Peacock | Lower Halliford | Chertsey |.
- Forster, W. E. (William Edward), 1818-1886, Wharfeside, Burley-in-Wharfedale, Leeds - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 October 1876; HWD 10.087; autograph letter signed
- Forster, W. E. (William Edward), 1818-1886, Wharfeside, Burley-in-Wharfedale, Leeds - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 10.088; autograph letter signed
- Forster, W. E. (William Edward), 1818-1886, Wharfeside, Burley-in-Wharfedale, Leeds - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 November 1876; HWD 10.086; autograph letter signed
- Forster, W. E. (William Edward), 1818-1886, Wharfeside, Burley-in-Wharfedale, Leeds - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 October 1876; HWD 10.089; autograph letter signed
- Galton, Francis, Sir, 1822-1911, 42 Rutland Gate S W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 20 November 1874; HWD 06.100; autograph letter signed
- Galton, Mary Anne Nicholson Douglas, Derwent Bank, Derby - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 February 1878; HWD 03.047; autograph letter signed
- Gayangos, Pascual de, 1809-1897, 104 Regt. Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 November 1867; HWD 03.006; autograph letter signed
- Gibson, S. A. Milner (Susannah Arethusa Milner), 1814-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.089; autograph letter signed
- Gibson, S. A. Milner (Susannah Arethusa Milner), 1814-1885, 3 Hyde Park Place, Cumberland Gate W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 June 1860; HWD 09.009; autograph letter signed
- Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809-1898, Hawarden - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 January 1856; MISC 3516 c; autograph letter signed
- Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809-1898, D. St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 May 1853; MISC 3516 b; autograph letter signed
- Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809-1898, 11 Careton House Terrace - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 November 1858; MISC 3516 d; autograph letter signed
- Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809-1898, 11 Careton House Terrace - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 February 1867; MISC 3516 e; autograph letter signed
- Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809-1898 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, MISC 3516 a; envelope only
- Gladstone, W. E. (William Ewart), 1809-1898, 11 Carlton House Terrace, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 November 1865; HWD 02.007; autograph letter signed
- Glenesk, Algernon Borthwick, Baron, 1830-1908 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 December 1863; HWD 05.090; autograph letter signed
- Glenesk, Algernon Borthwick, Baron, 1830-1908 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.088; autograph letter
  not signed; name written on back of letter.
- Goulburn, Edward, 1787-1868, 62 Upper Seymour Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1847; HWD 04.088; autograph letter signed
- Graham, James, Sir, 1792-1861 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 December 1860; HWD 08.044; autograph letter signed
- Graham, James, Sir, 1792-1861 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 March 1859; HWD 08.046; autograph letter signed
- Grant Duff, Mountstuart E. (Mountstuart Elphinstone), Sir, 1829-1906, The Athenaeum - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "14th"; HWD 05.056; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Castalia Rosalind, Countess, 1847-1938 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 July 1871; HWD 10.062; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Castalia Rosalind, Countess, 1847-1938 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 January 1878; HWD 09.089; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891, Bruton St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.068; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 August 1869; HWD 10.064; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891, 16 Bruton Street, London, W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 July 1871; HWD 10.063; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891, 18, Carlton House Terrace, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 February 1879; HWD 10.067; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891, 16 Bruton Street, London, W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 February 1872; HWD 10.069; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 July 1853; HWD 10.061; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 February 1872; HWD 10.065; autograph letter signed
- Granville, Granville George Leveson-Gower, Earl, 1815-1891 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 February 1872; HWD 10.066; autograph letter signed
- Greenwood, Frederick, 1830-1909, 14 Marine Park, Brighton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 December 1869; HWD 06.045; autograph letter signed
- Greenwood, Frederick, 1830-1909, Pall Mall Gazette, Northumberland Street, Strand - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 July 1868; HWD 06.046; autograph letter signed
- Greenwood, Frederick, 1830-1909, Pall Mall Gazette, Northumberland Street, Strand - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 January [no year]; HWD 06.047; autograph letter signed
- Greenwood, Frederick, 1830-1909, Pall Mall Gazette, Northumberland Street, Strand - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 January 1868; HWD 06.048; autograph letter signed
- Greenwood, Frederick, 1830-1909, Pall Mall Gazette, Northumberland Street, Strand - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 January 1868; HWD 06.049; autograph letter signed
- Greville, Charles, 1794-1865, Burton St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, [w/m = 186[2]?] "Thursday"; HWD 02.006; autograph letter signed
- Grote, Harriet, 1792-1878, The Ridgeway, Shiere, Guilford - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 March 1877; HWD 09.074; autograph letter signed
- Grote, Harriet, 1792-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 November 1869; HWD 10.079; autograph letter signed
- Grote, Harriet, 1792-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 November [w/m = 1868]; HWD 03.008; autograph letter signed
- Grote, Harriet, 1792-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 March 1874; HWD 04.031; autograph letter signed
- Grote, Harriet, 1792-1878, The Ridgeway, Shiere, Guildford - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 May 1873; HWD 03.001; autograph letter signed
- Grote, Mary A. E, 12 Saville Row W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 Dec [no year]; HWD 04.047; autograph letter signed
  niece of Mrs. Grote.
- Gurney, Russell, 1804-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 May [no year]; HWD 05.055; autograph letter signed
- Halifax of Monk Bretton, Mary Gray Wood, Viscountess, d. 1884, 10 Belgrave Sqre - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday Eveng."; HWD 09.079; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885, Thoresby Park, Ollerton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 December 1874; HWD 08.008; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 December 1874; HWD 09.035; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 November 1863; HWD 09.034; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 January 1866; HWD 09.033; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 January 1875; HWD 09.036; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 December 1874; HWD 08.014; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 December 1874; HWD 08.013; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 December 1874; HWD 08.009; autograph letter signed
- Halifax, Charles Wood, Viscount, 1800-1885 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 January 1856; HWD 08.010; autograph letter signed
- Hallam, Henry, 1777-1859 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 June [envelope w/m = 1834]; HWD 04.001; autograph letter signed
- Hallam, Henry, 1777-1859 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.067; autograph letter signed
- Hallam, Henry, 1777-1859 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 January 1848; HWD 10.010; autograph letter signed
- Harrington, Leicester Stanhope, Earl of, 1784-1862, Derby - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 January 1857; HWD 03.010; autograph letter signed
- Hatherley, William Page Wood, Baron, 1801-1881, 31 Great George Street, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 July 1871; HWD 06.071; autograph letter signed
- Hawtrey, Edward Craven, 1789-1862, Eccleshall Castle, Staffordshire - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 November 1860; HWD 02.053; autograph letter signed
- Hawtrey, Edward Craven, 1789-1862, Athenaeum, HWD 06.093
- Hawtrey, Edward Craven, 1789-1862, The Lodge, Eton College - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 April 1856; HWD 10.052; autograph letter signed
- Hayter, William Goodenough, Sir, 1792-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 January [no year]; HWD 09.051; autograph letter signed
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Temple - to [Mrs. Geale], 20 April 1856; HWD 09.091; autograph letter (copy)
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, St. James St - to Clanricarde, Harriet Canning de Burgh, Marchioness of, 1804-1876, HWD 09.066; autograph letter signed (copy?)
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Athenauem - to Tyndall, John, 1820-1893, 24 November 1871; HWD 10.107; autograph letter signed (copy)
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Privy Council Office [stationery] - to [My dear Porter], 5 March 1870; HWD 08.037; autograph letter signed
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, The Athenaeum - to "My dearest sisters", 2 February 1864; HWD 05.096; autograph letter signed
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Pencarrow, Bodmin - to [?], MISC 3490; autograph letter signed (copy?)
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, The Athenaeum - to "My dearest sister", 7 March [no year]; MISC 3491; autograph letter signed
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, The Athenaeum - to "My dearest sister", 27 March [no year]; MISC 3492; autograph letter signed
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Hotel Mirbeau, Paris - to Charleville, Catherine Maria Bury, Countess, 1762-1851, 18 November 1849; HWD 04.086; autograph letter signed copy
  In Carlisle's Selection.
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, The Athenaeum - to "My dearest sisters", 14 January [no year]; B'ANA 0598; autograph letter signed
  Filed in SC manuscript file; mentions Lord Byron.
- Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 St. James St - to "My dearest sisters", 20 April 1865; MISC 3493; autograph letter signed
  filed at end of Hayward Correspondence Files.
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, War Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 August 1859; HWD 08.073; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, Wilton House Salisbury - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 January 1859; HWD 08.071; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 March 1857; HWD 08.070; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, Wilton House Salisbury - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 January 1856; HWD 08.069; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, Wilton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 January 1841; HWD 08.075; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, 1 Grafton N - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Tuesday night"; HWD 08.076; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 08.074; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, Wilton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 May 1853; HWD 08.072; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, Wilton House, Salisbury - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 April 1855; HWD 02.048; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861, Wilton House, Salisbury - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 November 1856; HWD 02.047; autograph letter signed
- Herbert of Lea, Sidney Herbert, Baron, 1810-1861 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 March 1844; HWD 08.077; autograph letter signed
- Herbert, Mary Elizabeth Herbert, Baroness, 1822-1911, Savernake - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 January 1868; HWD 08.065; autograph letter signed
- Herbert, Mary Elizabeth Herbert, Baroness, 1822-1911, 38 Chesham Place S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 February 1872; HWD 08.068; autograph letter signed
- Herbert, Mary Elizabeth Herbert, Baroness, 1822-1911, Wilton House, Salisbury - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 December 1866; HWD 08.067; autograph letter signed
- Herbert, Mary Elizabeth Herbert, Baroness, 1822-1911, 38 Chesham Place S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 November 1866; HWD 08.066; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Henry Richard Vassall, Baron, 1773-1840, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 October 1838; HWD 04.041; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889, St. Anne's Hill, Chertsey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 December [no year]; HWD 06.030; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889, Stanhope Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 March 1865; HWD 02.022; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889, Naples - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 March 1858; HWD 07.043; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889, 9 Stanhope Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday July 24"; HWD 07.042; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 June 1859; HWD 02.017; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, Wed 23rd [no year; no month]; HWD 09.005; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889, Holland House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 July 1872; HWD 05.064; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 June 1868; HWD 02.018; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Sunday"; HWD 02.020; autograph letter signed
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 July 1872; HWD 02.021; autograph letter signed